嗨 大家好 这里没有人
Hi, everyone, none here.
没有 网上有个名单 这就是你们对我的了解
I go by none, a list online. That's what you all mostly know me for.
你现在在屏幕上看到的角色是我的虚拟头像 因为我一直被称为虚拟流媒体用户
The character you are seeing right now on the screen is my virtual avatar, as I've been known as a virtual streamer online.
我是一名自由艺术家 我把图形和设计放在动画作为职业课程
I'm a freelance artist. I took graphics and design place to the animation as vocational course.
但我真正想要的是插图制作 所以我更专注于这方面 毕业之后
But what really wanted was illustration making, and so I focus on that more. After I graduated.
我从小就开始画画
I have been drawing ever since I was little.
就我所能记得的 我曾经画过一个贴纸 我会在寄给我父亲的信上涂鸦 因为他曾经在海外工作 当我年轻的时候
And as far as I can remember, I used to draw a stickman, which I will doodle around on letters I sent to my father because he used to work overseas. When I was younger.
我会在字母上画我 我的妈妈和爸爸来表达我自己
I will draw me my mom and my dad on the letters to express myself.
我有多想他 我有多喜欢和我的家人在一起 在一个画面
How much I miss him and how much I enjoy seeing my family altogether. In one picture.
我想从我很小的时候起 我就一直出于某种原因在涂鸦
I think ever since I was little, I've just always been doodling for some reason.
主要是画人物 然后我会尝试用某种方式表现他们 比如他们的特点 他们的故事和他们的美学类型
Mostly draw people, which, then I will try and represent them in some way, like they're characteristics, their story and the type of aesthetics they have.
我记得当我第一次在电视上看 动物 时 我非常着迷于人们是如何被敌人风格所吸引的
I remember when I first watched Animal on TV, and I was really fascinated by how people are drawn in enemy style.
于是我受到启发 开始用同样的方式画敌人
And so I got inspired to start drawing in the same way as enemy.
从那时起 我开始创造自己的故事 创造自己的角色和受敌人启发的风格
Since then, I've started making my own stories and creating my own characters and enemy inspired style.
我基本上大部分时间都是在学校和家里画画 我只是非常热爱画画
I will draw basically most of the time in school at home. I was just really passionate about drawing.
我想说 这是我真正开始理解我想要什么样的职业的开始 这就是成为一名插画家
I'd say this was really the start of me understanding what type of career I want, and this is to be an illustrator.
我从传统艺术开始 当我从网上的朋友那里发现你可以画 我也开始尝试它
I started out with traditional art, and when I found out through my friends online that you can draw the, I started trying it out, too.
我有自己的平板电脑 从那以后我就一直在做数码产品
I got my own tablet around, and I've been doing digital ever since then.
在那一年 我也更加重视插画制作
I also took illustration making more seriously around that year as well.
我作品中最大的灵感来自于DanganRumpa的艺术家 以及 六 六 六
My biggest inspiration in my artworks is the artist of Dangan Rumpa, and the in six, six, six.
我真的很喜欢 DanganRumpa 中人物的脸 所以我决定把它添加到我自己的风格中
I really love the way faces are drawn in Dangan Rumpa characters, and so I decided to add that to my own style.
我认为鸽子是我最大的艺术灵感
I would consider pigeon as my biggest inspiration in art.
我真的很喜欢她错综复杂的生活 以及她对解剖学的类型化
I really love how intricate her life work is and how she stylizes her anatomy.
令人惊讶的是 她在她的插图中加入了如此多的细节 这也是我希望有一天能够实现的目标
It's amazing how much detail she puts into her illustrations. It's just something I would also love to achieve one day.
我想说的是 找到你自己的艺术档案 这真的是你计划好的事情吗
I will say that finding your own arts file, is it really something you plan out.
当你开始画画 并根据你最喜欢的艺术家尝试不同的绘画方式时 它就自然而然地来了
It just comes naturally as you start drawing and trying out different ways of drawing based on your favorite artist.
当你继续你的艺术之旅 你开始发展一种你觉得舒服的风格 你会认为它更能代表你
And as you continue in your art journey, you start developing a style which you find comfort in, and you will consider as something that represents you more.
艺术风格主要是关于表达你自己
Art styles are mostly about expressing yourself.
你认为最吸引你的衣领类型 你想画头发 眼睛等的方式
The type of collars which you think attracts you most, the type of way you want to draw hair, eyes and so on.
但是看了无数艺术家的作品 你开始发现了那种风格
But countless artist artwork to look at, did you start finding that one style.
它就像你最喜欢的美学的汇编 然后代表了你的工作的主要吸引力
It's like a compilation of your favorite aesthetics, which then represents the main attraction of your work.
我还喜欢观察不同的艺术作品 以及他们如何执行自己的想法和技术 使自己的艺术作品脱颖而出
One thing about me also is I love to observe different artworks and how they execute their ideas and techniques into making their artwork stand out.
我甚至倾向于观察现实生活中的人和物 所以我对如何将它们运用到我的插图中有了基本的了解
I even tend to observe people and objects in real life, so I would have a basic understanding on how I would apply them in my illustrations, later on.
我对艺术创作的建议是不要急于求成 清酒是缓慢的 不要害怕学习和尝试新事物
My advice and creating art is to not rush the process, the sake is slow and do not be afraid to learn and try new things.
因为如果你只是做艺术 就像你多年来一直做的那样 你将会对你所做的事情感到厌倦 你将再也找不到激情
Because if you just do art, how you've always done for many years, you will grow to become bored of what you do, and you will not find the passionate anymore.
但如果你尝试尝试更多的技巧 你会开始更喜欢你所做的事情
But if you try experimenting with more techniques, you will start loving what you do more.
这就是如何成为一个创造者 不断尝试新事物 创造新事物 最重要的是 永远不要失去灵感
That's how it is to be a creator, just keep trying new things, making new things, most importantly, never run out of inspiration.
经过多年的学习 我想把这些知识传授给你们
After years of learning many things, I want to pass on these knowledge to you.
希望我能在你的艺术之旅中帮助你 并爱你的创作 我也想谢谢你
And hopes that I could help you in your art journey and to love what you create. I would also like to thank you.
我们要加入这个班 谢谢你支持我
We're joining the class and for supporting me.
能有机会与你们分享我的激情和创作艺术 对我来说意义重大
Really mean so much to me to be able to have the chance to share my passion and creating art with you.
我也想更多地了解你
I would love to know more about you, too.
你可以在彗星中自由地介绍自己 是什么让你在创作艺术时受到启发
You'll free to introduce yourself in the comets and what made you feel inspired in creating art?
下节课 我将介绍这门课的介绍 我们在那儿见
Next class, I'll be going over the introduction to the course. I'll see you there.